Finding Aid for the Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) collection, 1964-1994
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Campaigns., 1974-1986, n.d..; Series 4.; Boxes 6, 9 and 14
  - Snuff., 1976, Mar-May, n.d..; Boxes 9 and 14
    - Signed Mann Theater petitions., 1976, Mar 22.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Programs., 1976-1983, n.d..; Series 5.; Boxes 2, 3, 8, 9 and 15
  All Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) non-campaign related events including fundraisers; slideshows, the presentation that chapter members showed to audiences nationwide and community events and conferences in which WAVAW participated or sponsored.
  - Slideshows., 1977-1987, n.d..; Boxes 2 and 3
    Versions of the script for the Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) slideshow, the presentation that chapter members showed to audiences nationwide and related correspondence. Slides include examples of Warner Communication, Inc.'s (WCI) subsidiary recording companies--Warner Bros., Elektra and Atlantic Records--and other record company album covers appealing to brutal and sadistic attitudes toward women, as well as other examples of abusive advertising. WAVAW's background and current tactics, position on corporate responsibility versus censorship, and its analysis of the marketing strategy represented by the slides are included in the accompanying slideshow script.
    - Censorship/1st Amendment., 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Community events., 1976-1983.; Boxes 2, 3, 8 and 9
    - Events Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) Participated in., 1983.; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Slideshows., 1977-1987, n.d..; Boxes 2 and 3
    - Forms and form letters., 1977, June; 1982, Jan-Feb, [n.d.].; 2 folders (Box 2, Folders 29 - 30)
      Order forms, slideshow check-list and order/payment forms.
  - Conferences., 1977-1983.; Boxes 2, 3 and 8
    Speaking engagements and/or attendance of Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) at conferences which include National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW)-sponsored conference "Law vs. Women"; American Public Health Association (APHA) annual conference; Barnard Conference, a 1982 academic conference on feminist perspectives on sexuality and the first National Women's Conference in Houston, Texas in Nov, 1977.
    - National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW) "Law vs. Women"., 1983, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Paper presented by Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) at National Council of Jewish Women NCJW-sponsored conference "Law vs. Women" and related correspondence.
  - Slideshows., 1977-1987, n.d..; Boxes 2 and 3
    - Orders/Payments., 1982-1983.; 2 folders (Box 2, Folders 31 - 32)
    - Slideshow script., 1977-1982.; 7 folders (Box 2, Folders 33 - 39)
      Drafts and originals of slideshow script, revisions, slide title lists/descriptions, notes and related correspondence.
      Includes Spanish version of slideshow script.
    - Slideshow scripts (other than WAVAW)., 1982, Apr, n.d..; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 40)
      Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media (WAVPM) and Women Against Pornography Slideshow scripts.
  - Conferences., 1977-1983.; Boxes 2, 3 and 8
    - American Public Health Association (APHA) annual conference., 1982-1983.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 31)
      abstract for WAVAW panel on violence against women as a public health issue
  - Slideshows., 1977-1987, n.d..; Boxes 2 and 3
    - Calendar., 1982.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Data Sheets for Slide Show Presentations., 1982-1984.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Community events., 1976-1983.; Boxes 2, 3, 8 and 9
    - Fight Back!., 1982, June.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Publicity flyer for Fight Back! Feminist Resistance to Male Violence event sponsored by Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) and Southern California Rape Hotline Alliance
    - Filmex leafletting., 1976, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fundraisers., 1978-1982.; Boxes 3 and 15
    Publicity announcements, media coverage and related correspondence for Holly Near benefit concert in March, 1980 Festival of Performing Arts fundraiser in May, 1982.
    - Holly Near benefit concert., 1980, March-Dec.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Publicity announcements and related correspondence for Holly Near benefit concert
      Includes correspondence re Lily Tomlin's pledge to match donations collected of up to $2,500.
  - Slideshows., 1977-1987, n.d..; Boxes 2 and 3
    - Slides, rape statistics and related correspondence., 1985, Jan.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Slideshow script drafts/revisions., 1987, Oct.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fundraisers., 1978-1982.; Boxes 3 and 15
    - Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) Festival of Performing Arts., 1982, May 21.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Publicity announcements and related correspondence.
  - Conferences., 1977-1983.; Boxes 2, 3 and 8
    - National Women's Conference (Houston, TX)., 1977, Nov.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Program from the first National Women's Conference "American Women on the Move" held in Houston in November, 1977.
  - Community events., 1976-1983.; Boxes 2, 3, 8 and 9
    - Women Against Violence in Pornography & Media (WAVPM) Orientation/Training., 1981, Oct.; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Orientation packet.
    - Kilbourne presentation re Killing Us Softly., 1982, Jan.; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Notes, publicity flyers, press releases, orbjectives and mailing labels re community education film Killing Us Softly - a film about the negative images of women in advertising.
    - Kilbourne presentation re Killing Us Softly Pre-/Post-Tests., 1982, Jan.; 4 folders (Box 9, Folders 51 - 54)
      Includes test results and analysis.
  - Fundraisers., 1978-1982.; Boxes 3 and 15
    - Holly Near benefit concert., 1978-1980.; 3 folders (Box 15, Folder 23 - 25)
      Publicity announcements and related correspondence, newspaper clippings, sheet music and concert tickets and receipts for Holly Near benefit concert
- Subject Files., 1971-1985, n.d..; Series 6.; Boxes 1, 3, 5, 28, 10, 14, 15 and 21
  Research material used by Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW). Included are articles, bibliographies, brochures, clippings, position papers, and newsletters relating to issues on battered women, boycotts, censorship, child sexual abuse, violence, television violence, the entertainment industry, the recording industry, pornography, rape, sadomasochism, and anti-pornography ordinances. Information concerning the Los Angeles Chapter's interaction with other women's organizations such as Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media (WAVPM), the Los Angeles Feminist Women's Health Center, the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR) and the Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) are included in the Subject Files.
  - Pornography., 1971-1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 5b and 21
    - L.A. anti-pornography ordinance., 1985, Apr-Sept.; 2 folders (Box 1, Folders 27 - 28)
      Press releases and statements issued by WAVAW and position paper drafts authored by Dani Adams, Executive Director of WAVAW, related to proposed L.A. anti-pornography civil rights law.
  - Anorexia., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Music Industry., 1976-1983.; Boxes 3, 5a and 15
    - WASP., 1983, May.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 22)
      Clippings and correspondence re band called "WASP" and reports of raw meat thrown into audience.
  - Organizations., 1974-1983.; Boxes 3, 14 and 15
    - Women's organizations., 1977, 1983, May.; 3 folders (Box 3, Folder 23 - 25)
      Publicity materials for MOTHER RAGE (f. 23), Women's Rand Action(f. 25) and YWCA (f. 24) and related correspondence. Includes WAVAW presentation to Pasadena YWCA Public Affairs Committee, May 16, 1977.
  - Music Industry., 1976-1983.; Boxes 3, 5a and 15
    - Articles on the music industry., 1976-1978.; 2 folders (Box 5, Folders 2 - 3)
      July, 1977 and Sept, 1977 issues of Music Retailer magazine and various articles and newsletters pertaining to women and the music industry and the music industry more broadly.
  - Issues re: Media Violence., 1976-1980.; Box 5a
    - Audiovisual aids., 1978-1982.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Media Violence., 1977-1978, n.d..; Box 5a
    - Durbin article: Pretty Poison., 1977, May.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Feshbach/Malamuth article: Sex and Aggression., 1978, Nov.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Issues re: Media Violence., 1976-1980.; Box 5a
    - Hillside Strangler., 1977, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Articles and press releases re rape-murders committed by the Hillside Strangler and memorial demonstration and related correspondence and notes.
  - Media Violence., 1977-1978, n.d..; Box 5a
    - Kilbourne article: Images of Women in TV Commercials., 1977.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Kilbourne, Jean Publicity., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Promotional materials for Kilbourne's slide presentation: The Naked Truth: The Cultural Conditioning of Women Via Advertising
  - Issues re: Media Violence., 1976-1980.; Box 5a
    - Men Against Sexist Violence., 1979, Aug.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Articles, notes, resolutions and related correspondence.
  - Music Industry., 1976-1983.; Boxes 3, 5a and 15
    - NARM., 1977, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Music Retailer magazine's special section on the annual conference of the National Association of Recording Merchandisers (NARM).
    - RIAA., 1976, Apr.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Music Retailer magazine's special section on the Record Industry Association of America (RIAA).
  - Issues re: Media Violence., 1976-1980.; Box 5a
    - Robber Bridegroom., 1976, Aug.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Program for Mark Taper's theater production of The Robber Bridegroom, notes and articles.
    - SF Conference re: Violence Against Women., 1976, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 13)
      San Francisco conference program, workshop descriptions, papers delivered, articles and notes.
    - Stack O Wheat Prints., 1980, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Articles, press releases and related correspondence re destruction of sex-violence photos, known as "The Incredible Case of the Stack O'Wheat Murders," in the University of California Santa Cruz (UCSC) library's Special Collections.
    - UCLA 1980 Seminar: Images of Women in Film., 1980, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Request for WAVAW's participation in UCLA Women's Film Festival seminar
  - Pornography., 1971-1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 5b and 21
    - Magazines: Hustler and Playboy., 1977-1982.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Articles relating to Hustler Magazine publisher Larry Flynt and Christie Hefner, head of Playboy.
    - Misc. Articles re: Pornography., 1971-1982, [n.d.].; 4 folders (Box 28, Folders 2 - 5)
      Oversized papers pulled and rehoused - NTFP News
    - Porn: preliminary source., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 28)
      Notes and draft of WAVAW authored paper.
    - Pornography and censorship., 1978, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Fact sheet and various articles.
  - Sado Masochism (S&M)., 1977-1983.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sexual harassment., 1975-1982.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Brochures, guidelines, statistics, articles and sexual harassment legislation.
  - Television violence., 1972-1980.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Violence., 1972-1979.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - WAVPM., 1978, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Women Against Violence in Pornography & Media (WAVPM) Membership form letters, welcome packets, publicity flyers and articles.
  - Rape., 1979.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes re certain individual named Dick Miller.
  - Sex therapy., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Organizations., 1974-1983.; Boxes 3, 14 and 15
    - Feminist Economics Network (FEN)., 1974-1976.; 2 folders (Box 14, Folders 16 - 17)
      Articles about the dissolution of FEN, position paper of the Los Angeles Feminist Women's Health Center, analysis by WAVAW, minutes of the Feminist Women's City Club meeting and related correspondence.
      Full-sized newspapers housed in oversized box
    - Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR)., 1977, Jan.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
      Information about the Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR) and its publications.
    - Testimony to Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR)., 1977, June.; 3 folders (Box 14, Folders 19 - 21)
      Complete script of Women Against Women Against Violence (WAVAW) testimony to Interfaith Center on Corporate Responsibility (ICCR).
  - Music Industry., 1976-1983.; Boxes 3, 5a and 15
    - NARM., 1977, Mar-Apr.; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 26)
      Report prepared by three members of WAVAW, Julia London, Dana Chalberg and Joan Belknap, concerning Century City Plaza Hotel Incident during National Association of Recording Merchandizers (NARM) Convention.
  - Organizations., 1974-1983.; Boxes 3, 14 and 15
    - Women's organizations., 1979, Feb - Nov/Dec.; 2 folders (Box 15, Folders 27 - 28)
      Article about the Los Angeles-based Woman's Building in Nov/Dec 1979 issue of Neworld and publicity announcement for first national conference of the National Women's Studies Association (NWSA).
  - Sex roles/behavior., 1977-1982.; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 48)
    Pull full-sized newspapers and rehouse in oversized box - Impact '79 and Together the Magazine of UCLA Women Sexism in Education
  - Pornography., 1971-1985, n.d..; Boxes 1, 5b and 21
    - L.A. anti-pornography ordinance., 1984-1985.; 2 folders (Box 21, Folders 8 - 9)
      Clippings, WAVAW-authored articles, notes and correspondence related to proposed L.A. anti-pornography civil rights law.
- Organizing., 1976-1982.; Series 7.; Box 4
  Background information and training materials covering ways to build an effective boycott; build grass-roots support; plan overall campaign strategy; generate media coverage and train organizers for Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) and speakers to present WAVAW's slide program. Includes examples of newsletter articles; questions frequently asked and their answers; fact sheets; bibliographies; publicity materials and sample activist packets and training materials from the National Organization for Women (NOW); the National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW); the National Trust for Historic Preservation; the Califia Organizers Collective and Midwest Academy (MWA).
  - Califia Community., 1976-1981.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Workshop materials, notes, Califia Community mailing lists and related correspondence.
  - California National Organization for Women (NOW) Organizing Materials., 1976 - 1977.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
    California National Organization for Women (NOW) consciousness raising workshop materials, fact sheets and bibliographies.
  - Guidelines: Working with Other Groups., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hassle Card: Warner Communications, Inc. (WCI) Boycott., 1976, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW) Workshop., 1981, Nov, 1982 Apr.; 2 folders (Box 4, Folders 6 - 7)
    Training materials from National Council of Jewish Women (NCJW), Los Angeles Section, workshop on women and activism.
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation., 1980-1982.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Organizing change., 1973-1976.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Various pamphlets and booklets, articles, bibliographies and fact sheets.
  - Organizing Collectives., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes from Califia Organizers Collective meeting
  - Organizing/Mobilizing Notes., 1976-1977.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Picketing guidelines: Warner Communications, Inc. (WCI) Boycott., 1976, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Leafletting Etiquette & Procedure
  - Public Service Advertising (PSAs)., 1976-1978.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Booklets, notes and WAVAW public service announcements
  - Questions People Will Ask: Warner Communications, Inc. (WCI) Boycott., 1976, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Questions asked during leafletting and proposed answers
  - Resolutions., 1977.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Proposed resolutions - 1977 NOW (National Organization for Women) National Conference
  - Strategy Chart Midwest Academy (MWA)., 1977, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Guidelines for planning an issue campaign from Midwest Academy (MWA)
  - Training materials., 1976-1980.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Drafts of Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) slideshow script and WAVAW guidelines.
  - UNO., 1979, Jan.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Notes from East L.A.-based United Neighborhoods Organization (UNO) training session.
  - Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) Organizing., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Direct action tactics and strategies
- WAVAW Activist Training., 1983, Feb.; Series 8.; Box 2
  Publicity fliers, agenda and orientation/training packets used for Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) activist training workshops dealing with publicity, slideshow presentations, WAVAW's history, future campaigns, and the basics of staffing the WAVAW office. Topics included: effective methods of protesting abusive images of women in media, effective public and private speaking, effective letter-writing, overcoming personal barriers, and how to organize yourself and your group.
  - Activist training forms., 1983, Feb.; 2 folders (Box 2, Folders 42 - 43)
    Publicity fliers, agenda and orientation/training packets used for WAVAW activist training workshops dealing with publicity, slideshow presentations, WAVAW's history, future campaigns, and the basics of staffing the WAVAW office. Topics included: effective methods of protesting abusive images of women in media, effective public and private speaking, effective letter-writing, overcoming personal barriers, and how to organize yourself and your group.
- Correspondence., 1976-1983, n.d..; Series 9.; Boxes 1, 2, 3, 7, 10, 14 and 15
  - Received/Answered Correspondence., 1983.; 1 folder (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Received Correspondence., 1983.; 1 folder (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Correspondence from individuals and organizations; includes publicity announcements, newsletters and brochures.
  - Received Correspondence., 1976, Oct.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Correspondence with United States Senate re rape legislation.
  - National Organization for Women (NOW) correspondence., 1978-1979.; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Received Correspondence., 1976-1979.; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Received/Answered Correspondence., 1977 - 1979.; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Victimology article submission correspondence., 1977, Oct - Nov.; 1 folder (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "In These Times" article correspondence., 1979, Mar.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Copy of letter sent to Ellen Willis, copy of record reviewer Bruce Dancis' "In These Times" article about WAVAW and copy of response from WAVAW that appeared in March 12, 1979 edition of "In These Times."
  - Received/Answered Correspondence., 1976-1982.; 12 folders (Box 10, Folders 4 - 16)
  - Feminist Alliance Against Rape Correspondence., 1976-1977.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Lesbian Tide correspondence., 1976, Feb-Mar.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Submissions and related correspondence.
  - Letters of Solicitation., 1976, Oct.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Correspondence from WAVAW to various organizations.
  - NCARL internal memos., 1977, Dec.; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Briefings by the National Committee Against Repressive Legislation (NCARL) re criminal code reforms.
  - Received Correspondence., 1979, Feb - 1983.; 5 folders (Box 14, Folders 26 - 30)
    Includes press releases from various feminist and women's organizations. Also includes correspondence with with the California Senate re abortion legislation.
  - Received/Answered Correspondence., 1976, Oct - 1978, Dec.; 6 folders (Box 14, Folders 31 - 36)
    1976, Dec - 1977, Jan correspondence covers dispute between WAVAW and Women's Building.
  - Correspondence Received., 1977-1980.; 4 folders (Box 15, Folders 37 - 40)
    Includes correspondence relating to Julia London article "Cultural Sanction of Violence"
  - Correspondence Received/Answered., 1977-1980.; 2 folders (Box 15, Folders 41 - 42)
- Audio-Visual materials., 1978-1983, n.d..; Series 10.; Boxes 6, 8, 11, 15, 18 and 20
  - Photos., 1979-1983, n.d..; Boxes 3, 6, 8 and 20
    - "Nine to Five"., 1980.; 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 58)
      Black and white photo signed by Jane Fonda, Lily Tomlin and Dolly Parton
  - Long playing (LP) record albums., 1978, n.d..; Box 8
    - (i'm the) Hillside Strangler (the Child Molesters)., 1978.; 1 long playing (LP) record album (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Photos., 1979-1983, n.d..; Boxes 3, 6, 8 and 20
    - Battered woman., n.d..; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Facial profile of battered woman
      Subject not identified
  - Long playing (LP) record albums., 1978, n.d..; Box 8
    - Free from the Fear/Ivory Tower (Sugar and Spite)., One 45 RPM record (Box 8)
      Album dedicated to victims of violence against women.
    - Hillside Strangler! (the Hollywood Squares) with sleeve., [n.d.].; one 45 RPM record (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photos., 1979-1983, n.d..; Boxes 3, 6, 8 and 20
    - Record album covers., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tape Reels., 1978, Feb.; Box 11
    - Album cover art - James Walker., 1978, February 17.; 1 tape reel (Box 11, Folder 12)
      20 minute tape reel recording by ABC
  - Tape cassettes., n.d..; Box 15
    - Music., n.d..; 9 tape cassettes (Box 15)
      A miscellany of dubbed tape cassettes by musicians such as Holly Near, Alix Dobkin and the Berkeley Women's Music Collective.
    - Roe vs. Wade., n.d..; 1 tape cassette (Box 14, Folder 37)
      Nine minute sound recording by Dani Adams.
  - Video cassettes., n.d..; Box 18
    - In Mourning & Rage., [n.d.].; 1 video cassette (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Record Companies Drag Their Feet., [n.d.].; 1 video cassette (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Photos., 1979-1983, n.d..; Boxes 3, 6, 8 and 20
    - Negatives., [n.d.]. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Slides., 1979-1983, n.d..; Box 20
    - Slides., 1979-1983, [n.d.].; 4 slide storage boxes (Box 20, Folders 2 - 12)
      Subjects include: WAVAW slideshows; WAVAW's Bloodline protest; billboards; store displays; Roe vs. Wade (Dani Adams) and bible passages/headlines.
      Some slides not identified.
- Ephemera., 1977-1982, n.d..; Series 11.; Boxes 6, 8, and 19
  Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW) t-shirts, buttons, stickers, rubber stamps and signs. Also includes a plaque for an award presented to WAVAW and a tablecloth used for an event.
  - Slogans and stickers., 1 folder (Box 6, Folder 59)
    bumper sticker white with red, color-imprinted lettering that reads "Don't Agonize: Organize!" and stickers with WCI campaign-specific slogans.
  - Stickers., [n.d.].; 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 7)
    pink with black, color-imprinted lettering that reads "THIS IS OFFENSIVE AND DEGRADING TO WOMEN."
  - Buttons., [n.d.]. (Box 19)
  - Plaque., 1982, July 29.; 1 plaque (Box 19)
    wooden, with white, color-imprinted plate lettering announcing award presented to WAVAW presented by the National Coalition Against Sexual Assault.
  - Rubber stamp., [n.d.].; 1 stamp (Box 19)
    WAVAW's mailing address
  - Sign., [n.d.].; 1 sign (Box 19)
    white poster board with black lettering spelling out "Women Against Violence Against Women."
  - Table cloth., 1977, Jan 30. (Box 19)
    yellow with red felt lettering spelling out: "Sisterhood Revival January 30, 1977."
  - T-shirts., [n.d.].; 4 t-shirts (Box 19)
    black t-shirts with white, color-imprinted WAVAW logo and yellow t-shirts with blue, color-imprinted WAVAW logo.